It's animation... with an attitude.
Bebe's Kids is a animation, comedy film directed by Bruce W. Smith.
When Robin meets the lovely Jamika he thinks he's in heaven.
But when he meets her friend Bebe's children, whom she
is looking after, he knows he's in hell.
Self, played by Robin Harris.
Robin Harris (voice), played by Faizon Love.
Jamika (voice), played by Vanessa Bell Calloway.
Leon (voice), played by Wayne Collins Jr..
Kahlil (voice), played by Marques Houston.
Lashawn (voice), played by Jonell Green.
Bebe's Kids ( BAY-bay; also marketed as Robin Harris' Bebe's Kids) is a 1992 American adult
animated comedy film produced by Hyperion Studio for Paramount Pictures.
Directed by Bruce W.
Smith in his directorial debut, it is based on a stand-up
routine created by comedian Robin Harris.
Harris died two years prior to the film's release; in the film,
he is voiced by Faizon Love in his acting debut.
As the first animated film to feature an entirely African-American main cast, it
co-stars Vanessa Bell Calloway, Marques Houston, Nell Carter and Tone Lōc.
Originally released theatrically on July 31, 1992, by Paramount
Pictures, Bebe's Kids was a critical and commercial failure.
Although its animation was praised, critics found fault
with its story, screenplay and humor.
Bebe's Kids grossed $8.4 million at the box office against a
budget of $10 million, becoming a box office bomb.
Despite this, it spawned a video game of the same name two
years later, which was likewise panned by critics.
The film explores themes of pirate, theme park, adult
animation, kids in peril, stand-up comedian.
The tone is lighthearted.